tweaking.com 2011-06-18

# MajorGeeks.com - Download Freeware and Shareware Computer Utilities.

MajorGeeks.Com respects its readers rights to privacy. 

MajorGeeks.Com occasionally collects information about its readers through polls or contest and giveaway registrations. The data collected is used to determine demographic information about the entire MajorGeeks.Com audience and to help target advertising. 

MajorGeeks.Com does not sell, rent, lease or allow any third parties to view or use the information collected unless the reader consents through the registration process. 

MajorGeeks.Com does maintain a mailing list that is used to keep 

_subscribers_ informed about certain deals, promotions, updates or events related. 

MajorGeeks.Com takes reasonable measures to keep the information disclosed secure. However, MajorGeeks.Com assumes no responsibility for any breach of security to this data. 

MajorGeeks Top Advertising Partners: (for your convenience)   
[TribalFusion](http://www.tribalfusion.com/) \- Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.exponential.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy.jsp) which alows for and opt-out.   
[Google](http://www.google.com/) \- Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) and [opt-out](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/view)   
[Vibrant Media](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/) \- Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/privacy.asp): Vibrant also has an [opt-out Option](http://intellitxt.com/opt_out/ch_optout.asp) if you like.   
[CleverBridge](http://www.cleverbridge.com/) \- Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.cleverbridge.com/?scope=contact&id=evhd7ETHEs&progress=privacyp)

For demographics, MajorGeeks.com uses [Quantcast](http://www.quantcast.com/) \- Their [Privacy Policy](http://www.quantcast.com/privacy). They also have an [opt-out option](http://www.quantcast.com/how-we-do-it/consumer-choice/opt-out). 

MajorGeeks.com does use other advertising networks, whose privacy policies will always be listed on their respective sites. Many of these comapnies belong to the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). They offer a page where you can select which companies you wish to opt-out of behavioral advertising meathods for it's members. You can find that [HERE](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp#). 

Now drop and give us 10100.
